A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1958-1970 FA400
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1965
  - International, 1965/100
    - International - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1965/100.E
      - Fellowships (Reel 9, Frame 1)
    - International - Social Sciences, 1965/100.S
      - Foreign Affairs (Books) (Reel 9, Frame 35)
    - International - Virus Studies, 1965/100.V
      - United Nations (World Health Organization) (Reel 9, Frame 37)
  - United States, 1965/200
    - Ab-Ad (Reel 9, Frame 42)
    - Agricultural Development Council (A-W) (Reel 9, Frame 145)
    - Af-Ag (Reel 9, Frame 405)
    - American (A) (Reel 9, Frame 529)
    - American (C) (Reel 9, Frame 597)
    - American (E-F) (Reel 9, Frame 886)
    - American (H-P) (Reel 10, Frame 1)
    - American Society (A-T) (Reel 10, Frame 268)
    - American (R-U) (Reel 10, Frame 396)
    - Ah-Ap (Reel 10, Frame 488)
    - Ar (Reel 10, Frame 683)
    - Asia Foundation (G-S) (Reel 10, Frame 789)
    - As (Reel 10, Frame 941)
    - At-Ay (Reel 11, Frame 1)
    - Ba (Reel 11, Frame 77)
    - Bio-Sciences Information Exchange (Reel 11, Frame 287)
    - Be-Bl (Reel 11, Frame 511)
    - Bo (Reel 11, Frame 704)
    - Bra-Bri (Reel 11, Frame 802)
    - Brookings Institution (B-S) (Reel 11, Frame 880)
    - Bro (Reel 11, Frame 972)
    - Bru-By (Reel 12, Frame 1)
    - Cab-Cal (Reel 12, Frame 50)
    - Cam-Car (Reel 12, Frame 179)
    - Cas-Ch (Reel 12, Frame 374)
    - Ci-Cl (Reel 12, Frame 582)
    - Columbia University (A-G) (Reel 12, Frame 689)
    - Columbia University (H-N) (Reel 12, Frame 835)
    - Columbia University (P-W) (Reel 12, Frame 968)
    - Coe-Col (Reel 12, Frame 1066)
    - Com-Con (Reel 13, Frame 1)
    - Coo-Cop (Reel 13, Frame 135)
    - Cornell (C-M) (Reel 13, Frame 249)
    - Cornell University (B-M) (Reel 13, Frame 291)
    - Cornell University (P-W) (Reel 13, Frame 421)
    - Cor-Cox (Reel 13, Frame 653)
    - Cr-Cu (Reel 13, Frame 809)
    - Da (Reel 13, Frame 931)
    - De (Reel 14, Frame 1)
    - Di-Du (Reel 14, Frame 222)
    - Education and World Affairs (Mexican Education) (Reel 14, Frame 449)
    - Education and World Affairs (A-W) (Reel 14, Frame 661)
    - Ea-Em (Reel 14, Frame 926)
    - En-Ex (Reel 14, Frame 1025)
    - F-Fe (Reel 15, Frame 1)
    - Film-Makers Cinematheque (Reel 15, Frame 68)
    - Fi (Reel 15, Frame 160)
    - Fl (Reel 15, Frame 295)
    - Ford Foundation (A-C) (Reel 15, Frame 372)
    - Ford Foundation (D-I) (Reel 15, Frame 515)
    - Ford Foundation (Latin American Program) (Reel 15, Frame 647)
    - Ford Foundation (K-W) (Reel 15, Frame 870)
    - Fo (Reel 16, Frame 1)
    - Fr-Fu (Reel 16, Frame 92)
    - Ga (Reel 16, Frame 437)
    - Ge (Reel 16, Frame 477)
    - Gh-Go (Reel 16, Frame 645)
    - Gr-Gu (Reel 16, Frame 775)
    - H-Hap (Reel 16, Frame 879)
    - Harvard University (B-E) (Reel 16, Frame 990)
    - Harvard University (F-L) (Reel 16, Frame 1090)
    - Harvard University (M-W) (Reel 17, Frame 1)
    - Har (Reel 17, Frame 85)
    - Has-Hay (Reel 17, Frame 341)
    - He (Reel 17, Frame 627)
    - Hi-Ho (Reel 17, Frame 874)
    - Hu (Reel 17, Frame 1059)
    - Indiana University (A-T) (Reel 18, Frame 1)
    - Institute of International Education (A-H) (Reel 18, Frame 143)
    - Institute of International Education (M-W) (Reel 18, Frame 254)
    - Institute (A-S) (Reel 18, Frame 336)
    - International (A-F) (Reel 18, Frame 432)
    - International Minerals and Chemical Corporation (E-W) (Reel 18, Frame 519)
    - International (M-S) (Reel 18, Frame 701)
    - I (Reel 18, Frame 761)
    - Ja-Je (Reel 18, Frame 996)
    - Johns Hopkins University (A-W) (Reel 19, Frame 1)
    - Jo-Ju (Reel 19, Frame 171)
    - K-Ka (Reel 19, Frame 260)
    - Ke (Reel 19, Frame 448)
    - Kh-Ku (Reel 19, Frame 511)
    - La (Reel 19, Frame 715)
    - Learning Institute of North Carolina (Reel 19, Frame 837)
    - Le (Reel 20, Frame 1)
    - Li (Reel 20, Frame 35)
    - Lo-Ly (Reel 20, Frame 211)
    - Maa-Mag (Reel 20, Frame 447)
    - Manhattan School of Music (Reel 20, Frame 637)
    - Mah-Mar (Reel 20, Frame 773)
    - Mas-May (Reel 20, Frame 853)
    - Mc (Reel 20, Frame 1001)
    - Me (Reel 21, Frame 1)
    - Michigan State University (A-S) (Reel 21, Frame 73)
    - Michigan State University (T-W) (Reel 21, Frame 188)
    - Mi (Reel 21, Frame 318)
    - Mo (Reel 21, Frame 468)
    - Mu-My (Reel 21, Frame 756)
    - National (A) (Reel 21, Frame 955)
    - National (B) (Reel 22, Frame 1)
    - National (C) (Reel 22, Frame 148)
    - National (E-F) (Reel 22, Frame 325)
    - National Institute of Health (C-W) (Reel 22, Frame 407)
    - National Institute (A-P) (Reel 22, Frame 595)
    - National (J-U) (Reel 22, Frame 711)
    - New Dimensions in Music (Reel 22, Frame 919)
    - New York (A-B) (Reel 22, Frame 1075)
    - New York (C) (Reel 23, Frame 1)
    - New York (H-S) (Reel 23, Frame 167)
    - New York (T-Z) (Reel 23, Frame 364)
    - Na-Ni (Reel 23, Frame 439)
    - North Carolina State College (A-W) (Reel 23, Frame 659)
    - Northern Illinois University (L-S) (Reel 23, Frame 795)
    - Northwestern University (A-V) (Reel 23, Frame 824)
    - Nutrition Foundation (P) (Reel 23, Frame 985)
    - No-Nu (Reel 23, Frame 1009)
    - Oa-Og (Reel 24, Frame 1)
    - Ohio (A-U) (Reel 24, Frame 164)
    - Ok-Ox (Reel 24, Frame 341)
    - Pan American Health Organization (A-Z) (Reel 24, Frame 632)
    - Pa (Reel 24, Frame 903)
    - Peabody Institute of the City of Baltimore (Reel 25, Frame 1)
    - Pennsylvania State University (Dickerson, Russell B.) (Reel 25, Frame 144)
    - Pennsylvania State University (D-W) (Reel 25, Frame 275)
    - Pe (Reel 25, Frame 426)
    - Pf-Ph (Reel 25, Frame 618)
    - Pi-Pl (Reel 25, Frame 753)
    - Po (Reel 25, Frame 885)
    - Princeton University (B-S) (Reel 26, Frame 1)
    - Purdue University (A-G) (Reel 26, Frame 223)
    - Purdue University (H-Y) (Reel 26, Frame 377)
    - Pr-Py (Reel 26, Frame 514)
    - Q (Reel 26, Frame 591)
    - Ra (Reel 26, Frame 599)
    - Re-Rh (Reel 26, Frame 704)
    - Ri (Reel 26, Frame 818)
    - Rockefeller (Reel 26, Frame 945)
    - Ro (Reel 27, Frame 1)
    - Rutgers University (D-V) (Reel 27, Frame 154)
    - Ru (Reel 27, Frame 272)
    - Sab-San (Reel 27, Frame 303)
    - Sar-Sc (Reel 27, Frame 523)
    - Se-Sm (Reel 27, Frame 725)
    - South Dakota State University (C-H) (Reel 27, Frame 938)
    - Southern Methodist University (B-R) (Reel 27, Frame 991)
    - Sn-Sq (Reel 28, Frame 1)
    - Stanford University (A-W) (Reel 28, Frame 175)
    - St (Reel 28, Frame 310)
    - Syracuse University (B-S) (Reel 28, Frame 503)
    - System Development Corporation (Reel 28, Frame 626)
    - Su-Sy (Reel 28, Frame 654)
    - Ta-Te (Reel 28, Frame 767)
    - Th-Tr (Reel 28, Frame 896)
    - Tu-Ty (Reel 28, Frame 994)
    - United States, Agency for International Development (A-L) (Reel 29, Frame 1)
    - United States, Agency for International Development (M-W) (Reel 29, Frame 191)
    - United States, Agriculture (A-F) (Reel 29, Frame 374)
    - United States, Agriculture (H-N) (Reel 29, Frame 590)
    - United States, Agriculture (O-W) (Reel 29, Frame 814)
    - United States (A-C) (Reel 29, Frame 880)
    - United States (H) (Reel 29, Frame 1037)
    - United States, Interior (C-U) (Reel 30, Frame 1)
    - United States (J-N) (Reel 30, Frame 14)
    - United States, State (A-W) (Reel 30, Frame 94)
    - United States (P-U) (Reel 30, Frame 278)
    - United States Advisory Commission on International Educational and Cultural Affairs (Reel 30, Frame 401)
    - United States Book Exchange (Reel 30, Frame 406)
    - United States Commission on Civil Rights (Reel 30, Frame 491)
    - United States Economic Research Foundation (Reel 30, Frame 495)
    - United States Information Agency (C-W) (Reel 30, Frame 500)
    - United States-Japan Cooperative Medical Science Program (Virus Diseases) (Reel 30, Frame 535)
    - United States News & World Report (Freeland, Stephen L.) (Reel 30, Frame 538)
    - United States Plywood Corporation (Brewer, Gene C.) (Reel 30, Frame 540)
    - United States-South Africa Leader Exchange Program (Reel 30, Frame 542)
    - United States Steel Foundation (Reel 30, Frame 564)
    - University (A-B) (Reel 30, Frame 571)
    - University of California (Arts) (Reel 30, Frame 630)
    - University of California (A-B) (Reel 30, Frame 769)
    - University of California (C-D) (Reel 30, Frame 999)
    - University of California (E-F) (Reel 30, Frame 1087)
    - University of California (Hardin, Charles M.) (Reel 31, Frame 1)
    - University of California (H-L) (Reel 31, Frame 147)
    - University of California (M-P) (Reel 31, Frame 335)
    - University of California (Vallier, Ivan A.) (Reel 31, Frame 530)
    - University of California (R-W) (Reel 31, Frame 667)
    - University of Chicago (A-W) (Reel 31, Frame 965)
    - University (C) (Reel 32, Frame 1)
    - University of Florida (A-Y) (Reel 32, Frame 36)
    - University (D-H) (Reel 32, Frame 173)
    - University of Illinois (A-T) (Reel 32, Frame 348)
    - University (I) (Reel 32, Frame 528)
    - University (K-L) (Reel 32, Frame 644)
    - University (Ma) (Reel 32, Frame 777)
    - University of Michigan (B-Y) (Reel 32, Frame 821)
    - University of Minnesota (B-M) (Reel 32, Frame 915)
    - University of Minnesota (O-W) (Reel 32, Frame 1038)
    - University (Mi-Mo) (Reel 33, Frame 1)
    - University of Oregon (Davies, James C.) (Reel 33, Frame 203)
    - University (N-O) (Reel 33, Frame 339)
    - University (P) (Reel 33, Frame 598)
    - University (R) (Reel 33, Frame 799)
    - University (S-T) (Reel 33, Frame 926)
    - University of Wisconsin (A-J) (Reel 34, Frame 1)
    - University of Wisconsin (K-Z) (Reel 34, Frame 123)
    - University (U-W) (Reel 34, Frame 293)
    - U (Reel 34, Frame 458)
    - Va-Ve (Reel 34, Frame 611)
    - Vi-Vo (Reel 34, Frame 740)
    - Wad-War (Reel 34, Frame 882)
    - Was-Wat (Reel 35, Frame 1)
    - Wau-Wer (Reel 35, Frame 195)
    - Wesleyan University (A-W) (Reel 35, Frame 297)
    - West Virginia University (B-N) (Reel 35, Frame 360)
    - Wes (Reel 35, Frame 433)
    - Wh (Reel 35, Frame 534)
    - Williams College (A-S) (Reel 35, Frame 583)
    - Wittenberg University (B-P) (Reel 35, Frame 615)
    - Wi (Reel 35, Frame 658)
    - Wo-Wy (Reel 35, Frame 824)
    - Yale University (B-R) (Reel 35, Frame 939)
    - Yale University (S) (Reel 35, Frame 1033)
    - Yale University (T-W) (Reel 9, Frame 1)
    - X-Y (Reel 9, Frame 124)
    - Z (Reel 9, Frame 290)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, 1965/200.A
      - B-T (Reel 9, Frame 352)
      - U-Y (Reel 9, Frame 480)
    - United States - Nursing, 1965/200.C
      - B-T (Reel 9, Frame 653)
      - U-V (Reel 9, Frame 711)
      - W (Reel 9, Frame 793)
    - United States - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1965/200.D
      - F-U (Reel 9, Frame 883)
    - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1965/200.E
      - A-Z (Reel 9, Frame 932)
    - United States - Declinations, 1965/200.F
      - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn (Behavioral Sciences) (Reel 9, Frame 1049)
    - United States - Humanitites and Arts, 1965/200.R
      - A-N (Reel 9, Frame 1054)
      - S-Y (Reel 37, Frame 1)
    - United States - Social Sciences, 1965/200.S
      - C-S (Reel 37, Frame 115)
      - U-Y (Reel 37, Frame 176)
    - United States - Virus Studies, 1965/200.V
      - American Committee on Arthropod-borne Viruses (Reel 37, Frame 368)
  - Guam, 1965/213
    - Hartz, Clyde (Reel 37, Frame 439)
  - Hawaii, 1965/214
    - Hawaii - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1965/214.D
      - University of Hawaii (Horticulture) (Reel 37, Frame 443)
  - Philippine Republic, 1965/242
    - Administration (Reel 37, Frame 456)
    - A-N (Reel 37, Frame 679)
    - P-T (Reel 37, Frame 750)
    - University of the Philippines (A-Q) (Reel 37, Frame 849)
    - University of the Philippines (R-U) (Reel 37, Frame 1031)
    - X-Y (Reel 38, Frame 1)
    - Philippine Republic - Medical Sciences, 1965/242.A
      - University (P-S) (Reel 38, Frame 35)
    - Philippine Republic - Nursing, 1965/242.C
      - University of the Philippines (Nursing School) (Reel 38, Frame 93)
    - Philippine Republic - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1965/242.D
      - University of the Philippines (Agriculture) (Reel 38, Frame 115)
      - University of the Philippines, Agriculture (Supplementary Material) (Reel 38, Frame 158)
    - Philippine Republic - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1965/242.E
      - Philippine Republic - Fellowships (Reel 38, Frame 424)
      - A-S (Reel 38, Frame 450)
    - Philippine Republic - Humanities and Art, 1965/242.R
      - University of the Philippines (L-P) (Reel 38, Frame 519)
  - Puerto Rico, 1965/243
    - Puerto Rico Nuclear Center (Barton, Marie) (Reel 38, Frame 567)
    - B-V (Reel 38, Frame 582)
    - Puerto Rico - Medical Sciences, 1965/243.A
      - University of Puerto Rico (Medical School) (Reel 38, Frame 705)
  - Virgin Islands, 1965/257
    - College of the Virgin Islands (Wanlass, Lawrence C.) (Reel 38, Frame 715)
  - South America and Central America, 1965/300
    Central America; South America
    - Administration (Reel 38, Frame 719)
    - Inter-American Institute of Agricultural Sciences (Blair, Enrique) (Reel 38, Frame 880)
    - Inter-American Institute of Agricultural Sciences (A-B) (Reel 39, Frame 1)
    - Inter-American Institute of Agricultural Sciences (Supplementary Material) (Reel 39, Frame 273)
    - Inter-American Institute of Agricultural Sciences (C-V) (Reel 39, Frame 346)
    - A-P (Reel 39, Frame 544)
    - South America and Central America - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1965/300.D
      - Inter-American Institute of Agricultural Sciences (Bean Improvement) (Reel 39, Frame 777)
    - South America and Central America - Social Sciences, 1965/300.S
      - South America and Central America (Reel 39, Frame 782)
  - Argentina, 1965/301
    - A-V (Reel 39, Frame 784)
    - Argentina - Medical Sciences, 1965/301.A
      - University of Salvador (Reel 40, Frame 1)
    - Argentina - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1965/301.D
      - A-U (Reel 40, Frame 3)
    - Argentina - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1965/301.E
      - Arias, Hipolito L. (Reel 40, Frame 16)
  - Bolivia, 1965/303
    - F-V (Reel 40, Frame 21)
    - Bolivia - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1965/303.E
      - Camargo-Gonzalez, Arnulfo E. (Reel 40, Frame 28)
  - Brazil, 1965/305
    - A-H (Reel 40, Frame 33)
    - I-O (Reel 40, Frame 169)
    - P-T (Reel 40, Frame 308)
    - University (B) (Reel 40, Frame 466)
    - University (M-R) (Reel 40, Frame 790)
    - University (S) (Reel 40, Frame 888)
    - V (Reel 40, Frame 1098)
    - Brazil - Medical Sciences, 1965/305.A
      - University of Campinas (Genetics) (Reel 40, Frame 1102)
    - Brazil - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1965/305.D
      - A-U (Reel 40, Frame 1119)
    - Brazil - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1965/305.E
      - Brazil (Reel 40, Frame 1158)
      - A-W (Reel 41, Frame 1)
    - Brazil - Social Sciences, 1965/305.S
      - Brazil (Reel 41, Frame 81)
      - C-U (Reel 41, Frame 94)
    - Brazil - Virus Studies, 1965/305.V
      - Instituto Adolfo Lutz (Reel 41, Frame 121)
  - Chile, 1965/309
    - Administration (Reel 41, Frame 124)
    - A-H (Reel 41, Frame 136)
    - I-S (Reel 41, Frame 262)
    - U-V (Reel 41, Frame 313)
    - Chile - Medical Sciences, 1965/309.A
      - University of Chile (Physiology) (Reel 41, Frame 447)
    - Chile - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1965/309.D
      - A-U (Reel 41, Frame 454)
    - Chile - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1965/309.E
      - Chile (Reel 41, Frame 476)
      - A-V (Reel 41, Frame 504)
  - Colombia, 1965/311
    - Colombia (Reel 41, Frame 603)
    - A-G (Reel 41, Frame 605)
    - Universidad del Valle (A-R) (Reel 41, Frame 722)
    - H-V (Reel 41, Frame 853)
    - Colombia - Medical Sciences, 1965/311.A
      - C-U (Reel 41, Frame 966)
    - Colombia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1965/311.D
      - A-U (Reel 41, Frame 983)
    - Colombia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1965/311.E
      - Colombia (Reel 41, Frame 1005)
      - A-Z (Reel 41, Frame 1062)
    - Colombia - Social Sciences, 1965/311.S
      - Universidad del Valle (P-S) (Reel 41, Frame 1148)
  - Costa Rica, 1965/313
    - B-U (Reel 42, Frame 1)
    - Costa Rica - Medical Sciences, 1965/313.A
      - University of Costa Rica (Reel 42, Frame 86)
    - Costa Rica - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1965/313.D
      - A-U (Reel 42, Frame 91)
    - Costa Rica - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1965/313.E
      - Echeverria, Jose H. (Reel 42, Frame 113)
    - Costa Rica - Social Sciences, 1965/313.S
      - University of Costa Rica (Social Sciences) (Reel 42, Frame 115)
  - Cuba, 1965/315
    - Rodriguez-Exposito, Cesar (Reel 42, Frame 122)
  - Ecuador, 1965/317
    - A-U (Reel 42, Frame 131)
    - Ecuador - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1965/317.D
      - National Agricultural Research Institute (A-C) (Reel 42, Frame 246)
    - Ecuador - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1965/317.E
      - Ecuador (Reel 42, Frame 250)
      - B-V (Reel 42, Frame 271)
  - Guatemala, 1965/319
    - A-U (Reel 42, Frame 322)
    - Guatemala - Medical Sciences, 1965/319.A
      - University of San Carlos (Medical School) (Reel 42, Frame 398)
    - Guatemala - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1965/319.D
      - Agriculture (G-M) (Reel 42, Frame 400)
    - Guatemala - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1965/319.E
      - B-M (Reel 42, Frame 410)
  - Haiti, 1965/320
    - D-S (Reel 42, Frame 436)
    - Haiti - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1965/320.D
      - Agriculture (B-D) (Reel 42, Frame 452)
  - Honduras, 1965/321
    - Escuela Agricola Panamericana (Muller, Albert S.) (Reel 42, Frame 456)
    - A-U (Reel 42, Frame 750)
    - Honduras - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1965/321.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 42, Frame 765)
    - Honduras - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1965/321.E
      - J-V (Reel 42, Frame 773)
  - Mexico, 1965/323
    - A-F (Reel 42, Frame 785)
    - Guadalajara Autonomous University (G-M) (Reel 42, Frame 822)
    - G (Reel 42, Frame 1044)
    - National Agricultural Research Institute, Valdes (Supplementary Material) (Reel 42, Frame 1067)
    - L-N (Reel 43, Frame 1)
    - University of Sonora (Supplementary Material) (Reel 43, Frame 238)
    - P-W (Reel 43, Frame 261)
    - Mexico - Medical Sciences, 1965/323.A
      - Universidad de Guanajuanto (Medical School) (Reel 43, Frame 441)
    - Mexico - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1965/323.D
      - University (G-S) (Reel 43, Frame 444)
    - Mexico - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1965/323.E
      - Mexico (Reel 42, Frame 783)
        General note
        Marked up incorrectly as Series 322E. Separated from bulk of Series 323E material.
      - Mexico (Reel 43, Frame 453)
      - A-Y (Reel 43, Frame 494)
  - Nicaragua, 1965/325
    - University of Nicaragua (Tunnerman Bernheim, C.) (Reel 43, Frame 650)
  - Republic of Panama, 1965/327
    - G-U (Reel 43, Frame 652)
    - Republic of Panama - Medical Sciences, 1965/327.A
      - University of Panama (Medical School) (Reel 43, Frame 746)
    - Republic of Panama - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1965/327.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 43, Frame 754)
  - Peru, 1965/331
    - Pontifical Catholic University of Peru (Reel 43, Frame 769)
    - A-V (Reel 43, Frame 920)
    - Peru - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1965/331.D
      - A (Reel 44, Frame 1)
    - Peru - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1965/331.E
      - C-R (Reel 44, Frame 111)
  - El Salvador, 1965/333
    - D-U (Reel 44, Frame 145)
  - Dominican Republic, 1965/335
    - I-M (Reel 44, Frame 228)
  - Uruguay, 1965/337
    - P-R (Reel 44, Frame 234)
    - Uruguay - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1965/337.D
      - University of Montevideo (Agronomy) (Reel 44, Frame 238)
  - Venezuela, 1965/339
    - A-V (Reel 44, Frame 240)
    - Venezuela - Nursing, 1965/339.C
      - National School of Nursing (Caracas) (Reel 44, Frame 283)
    - Venezuela - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1965/339.D
      - Agriculture (Rios, Carlos Eduardo) (Reel 44, Frame 289)
    - Venezuela - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1965/339.E
      - Venezuela (Reel 44, Frame 297)
  - Great Britain, 1965/400
    - C-O (Reel 44, Frame 300)
  - England, 1965/401
    - A-H (Reel 44, Frame 334)
    - I-L (Reel 44, Frame 514)
    - M-O (Reel 44, Frame 693)
    - P-S (Reel 44, Frame 840)
    - University (B-K) (Reel 44, Frame 968)
    - University (L-T) (Reel 45, Frame 1)
    - W (Reel 45, Frame 152)
    - England - Medical Sciences, 1965/401.A
      - University College Hospital (Medical School) (Reel 45, Frame 234)
    - England - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1965/401.D
      - University College, Nottingham (Agriculture) (Reel 45, Frame 236)
    - England - Declinations, 1965/401.F
      - Higgs, E. S. (Reel 45, Frame 249)
    - England - Social Sciences, 1965/401.S
      - British Institute of Economic Research (Reel 45, Frame 256)
  - Ireland, 1965/403
    - C-T (Reel 45, Frame 259)
  - Scotland, 1965/405
    - A-U (Reel 45, Frame 276)
    - Scotland - Nursing, 1965/405.C
      - University of Edinburgh (Reel 45, Frame 301)
    - Scotland - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1965/405.D
      - University of Edinburgh, Genetics (Supplementary Material) (Reel 45, Frame 307)
      - University of Edinburgh (Zoology) (Reel 45, Frame 378)
  - Wales, 1965/407
    - K-P (Reel 45, Frame 402)
  - Australia, 1965/410
    - A-W (Reel 45, Frame 408)
    - Australia - Medical Sciences, 1965/410.A
      - University (N-S) (Reel 45, Frame 569)
    - Australia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1965/410.D
      - University (Q-S) (Reel 45, Frame 572)
    - Australia - Declinations, 1965/410.F
      - Archway Rehabilitation Center (Reel 45, Frame 606)
  - New Zealand, 1965/418
    - L-U (Reel 45, Frame 619)
    - New Zealand - Nursing, 1965/418.C
      - New Zealand Registered Nurses' Association (Reel 45, Frame 630)
  - Caribbean Region, 1965/420
    - Freund, Gerald (Supplementary Material) (Reel 45, Frame 634)
    - C-M (Reel 45, Frame 658)
  - Guyana, 1965/423
    - University of Guyana (Drayton) (Reel 45, Frame 688)
  - Canada, 1965/427
    - A-K (Reel 45, Frame 700)
    - M-Z (Reel 45, Frame 837)
    - Canada - Medical Sciences, 1965/427.A
      - McGill University (Medical School) (Reel 45, Frame 1027)
    - Canada - Nursing, 1965/427.C
      - University of Toronto (School of Nursing) (Reel 45, Frame 1029)
  - Barbados, 1965/435
    - M (Reel 45, Frame 1036)
  - Jamaica, 1965/437
    - B-W (Reel 46, Frame 1)
  - Trinidad and Tobago, 1965/451
    Universities and colleges -- Trinidad and Tobago -- West Indies
    - D-V (Reel 46, Frame 243)
  - Windward Islands, 1965/455
    - R-S (Reel 46, Frame 305)
  - Sri Lanka, 1965/462
    - A-U (Reel 46, Frame 329)
  - Hong Kong, 1965/463
    - C-U (Reel 46, Frame 347)
  - India, 1965/464
    - 464 (Reel 46, Frame 364)
    - A-D (Reel 46, Frame 374)
    - Finance (Reel 46, Frame 546)
    - G-J (Reel 46, Frame 630)
    - K-T (Reel 46, Frame 888)
    - University of Delhi (B-D) (Reel 46, Frame 1116)
    - University of Delhi (E) (Reel 47, Frame 1)
    - University of Delhi (F-S) (Reel 47, Frame 146)
    - U-W (Reel 47, Frame 303)
    - India - Medical Sciences, 1965/464.A
      - A-V (Reel 47, Frame 370)
    - India - Nursing, 1965/464.C
      - A-V (Reel 47, Frame 398)
    - India - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1965/464.D
      - A-M (Reel 47, Frame 461)
    - India - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1965/464.E
      - India (Reel 47, Frame 479)
    - India - Humanitites and Art, 1965/464.R